{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Optimism crypto chain.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is Optimism?",
      "answers": ["L2", "Coin", "Token"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Optimism is built on?",
      "answers": ["ETH", "BTC", "SOL"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP token use?",
      "answers": ["Gov", "Trade", "Farm"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Optimism boosts?",
      "answers": ["Speed", "Cost", "Security"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP Labs is?",
      "answers": ["Team", "DAO", "Tech"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "When was OP launched?",
      "answers": ["2020", "2021", "2022"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "OP uses?",
      "answers": ["Rollup", "Plasma", "Shards"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP governance?",
      "answers": ["DAO", "Board", "Voting"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Optimism's aim?",
      "answers": ["Scal", "Save", "Secure"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP token type?",
      "answers": ["ERC20", "ERC721", "BEP20"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Rollups are?",
      "answers": ["Layer2", "Layer1", "Side"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP reduces?",
      "answers": ["Gas", "Stake", "Nodes"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP's network?",
      "answers": ["Main", "Test", "Side"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP partners?",
      "answers": ["Uniswp", "Binance", "Kraken"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Main goal of OP?",
      "answers": ["Scal", "Decent", "Private"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP handles?",
      "answers": ["Txs", "Blocks", "Nodes"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP token utility?",
      "answers": ["Gov", "Pay", "NFTs"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP security?",
      "answers": ["ETH", "BTC", "SOL"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP launched on?",
      "answers": ["ETH", "BTC", "BSC"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "OP's main use?",
      "answers": ["Apps", "Games", "Files"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
